realeyesit.com 2015-05-23

# Realeyes - Privacy

Realeyes OU (“Realeyes”) conducts market research to help improve web content and advertising. Our proprietary software is used to track participants' facial features and to analyse their emotional response to on-screen media.

While Realeyes is committed to making the participant experience as natural and as unobtrusive as possible, we also take our data privacy responsibilities very seriously. Our Privacy Policy tells you how we look after and use the Personal Information that we collect from participants in our Realeyes products. Please read this carefully. When you use our services, you are agreeing to our Privacy Policy.

Safeguarding your privacy is of the utmost importance.

1.    Realeyes has a strict opt-in research policy. We only collect study data (including facial recordings) from participants who have given their explicit consent by allowing access to their webcam prior to each media viewing session.  
2.    Any personal information (see definition below) that we collect from you will be treated as strictly confidential.

## Data Security is our priority

All personal data will be stored in a secure location. We use industry standard technical and organizational security measures to protect your data against unauthorized disclosure or processing. Furthermore, Realeyes will never sell your Personal Information to our clients.

## What Personal Information do we collect?

When you consent to participate in our study, we collect facial recordings, IP addresses and website usage information using cookies.  
Occasionally we also do surveys where we invite participants from special panels. We may collect additional non-personally identifying demographic information (such as interests, gender and age group) from these participants who have consented to providing this information.

## How will we use your Personal Information?

Realeyes specialises in market research. Your participation in our studies is highly valued. We are interested in your reactions to on-screen media so that we can help improve web content and advertising. We will never try to sell you any products or services and we will never share your Personal Information with anyone engaged in marketing, telemarketing or other solicitous activities.

Realeyes may to use anonymized study data to assess quality assurance and to help improve software and reporting capabilities.

We may share your information in limited ways as part of our secure business processes:

  * We work with trusted partners to perform tasks on our behalf and we may need to disclose Personal Information to them so that they can perform these tasks. However, these companies are bound by confidentiality obligations and do not have any independent right to use Personal Information beyond what is necessary to assist us

  * We may share your Personal Information, where appropriate, with any member of our group of companies

  * When the law requires us to disclose your information, we will comply

  * If there is a change in the ownership of Realeyes or any of our assets, we may disclose Personal Information to the new or prospective investor.

We may display targeted advertisements based on emotion data, anonymised information, Personal Information and/or information about your browsing activities. No personal Information will be provided to the advertiser directly by Real Eyes when we display a targeted advertisement. However, by interacting with or viewing an advertisement you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will collect data from you and/or make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the advertisement.

## How long do you keep Personal Information for?

We store Personal Information for as long as it is required solely for our research and business purpose. When Personal Information is no longer required, we will delete it from our systems.

## Cookies

Cookies are small text files that we place on your computer or device to allow us to track our research and assess participant behaviour information. We use third party service providers (such as Google analytics) to track usage and interaction with the media players. The cookies cannot identify you.

If you opt out from using participating in our study, we will place a cookie on your computer as it is required to remember your choice. If you delete your cookies from your browser, you will also be deleting your opt out and you may be asked to participate in our study again.

## Child Protection

Realeyes does not knowingly obtain information, study data, or survey responses from participants under the age of 18, unless there is consent from a parent or legal guardian. Should we discover that any data has been collected from a participant under the age of 18, without consent of a parent or legal guardian, we will immediately delete it.

## International transfer of Personal Information

We may transfer your Personal Information to countries outside of the European Economic Area EEA (such as the US), but only to companies we trust. This includes Real Eyes group companies or carefully selected business partners that agree to “Safe Harbor” certification or equivalent protections. We do this for our data management and business purposes, in particular, for outsourced data processing by organisations on our behalf. We take appropriate steps to ensure your information is adequately protected. If you do not agree to this, please do not use our services.  

## Contacting us

Please contact us if you have any comments or questions about information that we hold or about our Privacy Policy

  * Send an email to info@realeyesit.com under the subject heading "Privacy Policy"
  * Write to us at 79 Wardour Street, London W1D 6QB, UK

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of changes by posting an announcement on our service or website. You are bound by any changes to our Privacy Policy when you use our service after you are notified (by an announcement on our service or website) of these changes.

## What does personal information mean?

Personal Information means anything that can be used to identify you, including facial recordings and IP addresses that we collect as you participate in our study. 

If you do not agree with our Privacy Policy, please do not participate in Realeyes market research studies at this time.

Page Align: Left
